(Sheldon:)You can defecate in peace.
That's a win for both of us.
(Penny:)But...
(Sheldon:)Until this matter is resolved,
(Sheldon:)I would like you
(Sheldon:)to wear this sweater.
(Sheldon:)With nothing underneath it.
(Leonard:)That's stupid. Why?
(Sheldon:)You say it's itchy and uncomfortable.
(Sheldon:)I say situations like this
make me feel the same way.
(Leonard:)I'm telling you, try the hanger.
(Sheldon:)Put it on.
(Sheldon:)Let's share the experience.
(Leonard:)You got it.
(Leonard:)If this sweater shuts you up,
I'm gonna make a fortune
(Leonard:)selling them to everyone we know.
(Leonard:)Now all I need to do
(Leonard:)is head down to the video store
(Leonard:)and return the DVD.
(Sheldon:)Oh, did I forget to tell you?
(Sheldon:)That store went out
of business years ago.